<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gospel Trumpet Radio</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_us">Greetings friend. You may wonder who we are. We are not a denomination. We are the church of the living God, as we read about in the New Testament. \n\n  For too long, the religious world has seen a departure from the apostolic message of the church of God. This fact is evidenced by the prevailing condition of spiritual deadness and insensitivity, the drift to worldliness, the decline in deep spirituality, the loss of evangelistic zeal, and the increasing dependence on tradition, man-rule, and intellectual understanding of the doctrine. God no longer tolerates these dark conditions. He is now sending a Holy Ghost awakening. This is a divine move of the Spirit, ordained by God and prophesied of in Revelation and other scriptures. God is restoring His church and calling all of His true children out of every sect and schism back to the one fold. \n\n   It is time for every one of God’s children to hear and obey, in fullness, God’s precious Word. He is calling us to be the church of God in the apostolic sense; not in name only, but in reality and power. Let the scriptures settle the matter. God is not coming for a defeated, divided, spiritually ragged, powerless church. He is coming for a glorious church, not having spot, or wrinkle, or any such thing (Eph. 5:27). \n\n  In this time of restoration, we rejoice as the apostolic message of the church is once more being sounded forth clearly, in its purity and power, to gather unto God His glorious, blood-bought bride, the church of God. She is now making herself ready for the Saviour’s soon return. \n\n  We are zealous to meet with all lovers of truth and would love to hear from you! \n\n  “The Spirit and the bride say, Come. And let him that heareth say, Come. And let him that is athirst come. And whosoever will, let him take the water of life freely.” Rev. 22:17.</string>
</resources>
